<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project on Michael Mao</title><link>https://michaelmao.me/project/</link><description>Recent content in Project on Michael Mao</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:09:28 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://michaelmao.me/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HUSTL</title><link>https://michaelmao.me/project/hustl/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:09:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://michaelmao.me/project/hustl/</guid><description>Hyperlapse processed with HUSTL
Links: GitHub Repo, Project Writeup Members: Michael Mao, Jiaju Ma, James Li Duration: Spring 2019
Overview Making good hyperlapse videos is difficult. It usually requires photographers to take photos between consistent distance intervals and keep the height of the camera and the direction of the lens steady and smooth. Alternatively, they can mount their camera on expensive steadicams or gimbals. To make creating high-quality hyperlapses easier, we present HUSTL (Hyper-Ultra-Super-Time-Lapse), an open source three-stage software pipeline based on the state of the art academic research papers.</description></item><item><title>Personal Website</title><link>https://michaelmao.me/project/personal-website/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2022 00:36:54 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://michaelmao.me/project/personal-website/</guid><description>Home page layout
Links: GitHub Repo, Example Blogpost
Overview This personal website is made from scratch using Hugo framework. The color scheme is inspired by Nord theme and all code blocks uses Nord color scheme. The website is responsive and is designed for both mobile and desktop, and supports both vertical and horizontal screen orientations.
Home Page and Blogging The website offers a customizable home page or landing page to suit the need of different users.</description></item><item><title>OKAI</title><link>https://michaelmao.me/project/okai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2023 13:09:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://michaelmao.me/project/okai/</guid><description>OKAI viewed on multiple devices
Links: website Members: Jiaju Ma, Michael Mao, Yimei Hu Duration: Sep 2018 - May 2019 Pageviews: 160k+ Users: 38k+
Overview OKAI is an interactive introduction to Artificial Intelligence (AI). The project aims to demystify and introduce machine learning and deep learning concepts to a broader audience with limited or no background in computer science. It utilizes web-based interactive graphics and animations to visualize the working principles of a simple feed-forward neural net classifier on the MNIST dataset.</description></item></channel></rss>